https://www.ancientfaces.com/content/terms

Community
What is AncientFaces?
AncientFaces is 100% Free
Success Stories
Join the community - it's free!
What does the
do?
Add Photos & Bios
Forgot your password?
Terms of Use
Welcome to AncientFaces (http://www.ancientfaces.com).
We don’t take ownership of the photos, the user retains that, you are just giving us the ability to display on AncientFaces and our social media channels.
If you visit or participate at AncientFaces, you accept these conditions.
We reserve the right to change these conditions at any time.
Your continued use of the site following any changes to these conditions means that you accept those changes.
PRIVACY
Please review our Privacy Policy, which also explains the practices of AncientFaces.
COPYRIGHT
All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, photos, data compilations, and software,
is the property of AncientFaces or its content suppliers and protected by United States copyright laws. The compilation of all
content on this site is the exclusive property of AncientFaces and protected by United States copyright laws. All photos contained
on AncientFaces.com are protected by copyright protection and may NOT be downloaded and/or used in ANY commercial environments
included but not limited to other websites.
LICENSES AND SITE ACCESS
AncientFaces grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of this site and not to download or modify it, or
any portion of it, except with express written consent of AncientFaces. This license does not include any resale or commercial
use of this site or its contents; any collection and use of photos or documents; any collection and use of
any information; or any use of data mining and gathering tools. All photographs and any other materials
submitted by users are owned or licensed by the submitter and/or AncientFaces. You may view, download, and print material from
this site only for your personal and noncommercial use. You may not post any material on another web site or on a computer network
without the submitter's permission. You may not post any material unique to AncientFaces on another web site or on a computer
network without AncientFaces' permission. You may not use this site, or information found at this site, for selling or promoting
products or services, soliciting clients, or any other commercial purpose including replication on any other website. Any
unauthorized use terminates the permission or license granted by AncientFaces. You are granted a limited, revocable, and
nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to AncientFaces.com so long as the link does not portray AncientFaces, its affiliates,
or their materials, products, or services, in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise offensive matter. You may not use
any AncientFaces' logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without express written permission.
YOUR ACCOUNT
If you use this site and are a Registered User, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality
of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept
responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. AncientFaces and its
affiliates reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel
orders in their sole discretion.
UPLOADING PHOTOS AND OTHER CONTENT
Thank you for sharing your family history at AncientFaces. When you add your information at AncientFaces
we DO NOT take ownership of your photos or family records. You retain all ownership rights. By participating
you're giving us the ability to display your family history on AncientFaces, our social media channels and the ability to promote your content.
IN CONSIDERATION of and for the use of AncientFaces (https://www.ancientfaces.com) uploading facilities it is agreed as follows: By submitting
any material, including photographs, and/or accompanying text, you thereby automatically grant
(or warrant that the owner of such rights has expressly granted) to AncientFaces an irrevocable, royalty-free, non-exclusive,
transferable, and universal right and license to use and display the said submitted material in conjunction with this site
without compensation to you.
You also grant others to download and use the photos, and/or other submitted content for their own private use,
including but not limited to personal genealogical research.
Those who download photos, and/or other submitted
content can not profit from this information in any manner.
By such submission, you also warrant that you have the necessary rights or ownership to grant permission to display the image
and/or submitted content. AncientFaces specifically disclaims any copyrights in your image or text, except that AncientFaces
as a whole is a copyrighted concept of its owners.
You specifically and explicitly agree that you will not upload images of a
pornographic, defamatory, or inappropriate nature. You also agree that you will not upload other binary content such as software
programs, illegal copies of software programs, or knowingly upload files containing a computer virus or material in violation
of copyright law.
Your name and email address are required in the event someone researching your content wishes to contact you. It will, however,
not be sold to any third party or used for anything but normal communications purposes. AncientFaces and its editors reserve
the right to refuse or to remove a submission for any reason. Any content that does not meet editorial standards will not be
included in AncientFaces.
You grant AncientFaces an irrevocable right to replicate and/or modify your submitted material in any manner deemed appropriate
by AncientFaces, it's editors, and owners.
AncientFaces and its editors, and the owners of this site take no responsibility for
checking the veracity of information, claims, and copyright status of material presented here. AncientFaces services are offered
on an AS IS basis, with no express or implied warranty. Although AncientFaces does not normally pre-check for copyright violation,
any content reported to the editors by authorized representatives of a copyright owner as constituting an infringement will be
removed as soon as possible.
REVIEWS, COMMENTS, COMMUNICATIONS, AND OTHER CONTENT
Visitors may send email; post reviews and comments, and other content; and upload suggestions, ideas, comments,
questions, or other information, so long as the content is not illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory,
invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, or otherwise injurious to third parties or
objectionable, and does not consist of or contain software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation,
chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of "spam". You may not use a false email address, impersonate any person or
entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of other content. AncientFaces reserves the right to remove or edit such
content, but does not regularly review posted content. If you do post content or upload material, and unless we indicate
otherwise, you grant AncientFaces and its affiliates a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully
sub licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and
display such content throughout the world in any media. You grant AncientFaces and its affiliates and sublicenses the right
to use the keywords that you upload in connection with such content, if that you post; that the content is accurate;
that use of the content you supply does not violate this policy and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and
that you will indemnify AncientFaces or its affiliates for all claims resulting from content you supply. AncientFaces has
the right to monitor and edit or remove any activity or content. AncientFaces takes no responsibility and assumes no
liability for any content posted by you or any third party.
OTHER BUSINESSES
Parties other than AncientFaces and its subsidiaries may advertise or sell products or services at AncientFaces. We are
not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of, any of these businesses or
individuals or the content of their listings or web sites. AncientFaces does not assume any responsibility or liability
for the actions, product, and content of any third parties. You should carefully review their Customer Service Policy
before purchasing from any 3rd party.
LINKING
For your convenience, AncientFaces contains links to other genealogy and family web sites. These
sites are not maintained or controlled by us, and we are not responsible for their content.
Although we have made a good faith effort to link only to tasteful, appropriate sites, some may
contain inappropriate or objectionable material. If you find such material through AncientFaces
please notify us immediately.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
This site is provided by AncientFaces on an 'as is' and 'as available' basis. AncientFaces makes no
representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of this site or
the information, content, materials, or products included on this site. You expressly agree that
our use of this site is at your sole risk. To the full extent permissible by applicable law,
AncientFaces disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied
warranties of seller ability and fitness for a particular purpose. AncientFaces does not warrant
that this site, its servers, or email sent from AncientFaces are free of viruses or other harmful
components. AncientFaces will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use of
this site, including but not limited to direct, indirect, incidental, punitive, and consequential
damages.
APPLICABLE LAW
By visiting AncientFaces, you agree that the laws of the state of California, without regard to
principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Conditions of Use and any dispute of any sort
that might arise between you and AncientFaces or its affiliates.
DISPUTES
Any disputes relating in any way to your visit to AncientFaces shall be submitted to confidential
arbitration in San Jose, California, except that, to the extent you have in any manner violated
or threatened to violate AncientFaces intellectual property rights, AncientFaces may seek
injunctive or other appropriate relief in any state or federal court in the state of California,
and you consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in such courts. Arbitration under this
agreement shall be conducted under the rules then prevailing of the American Arbitration
Association. The arbitrator's award shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any
court of competent jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no
arbitration under this agreement shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party
subject to this agreement, whether through class arbitration proceedings or otherwise.
What Personal Information about visitors does AncientFaces gather?
Information You Give Us:
We collect personal information such as your name, email address,
and other basic information to provide you with an enhanced
experience at AncientFaces. Your information is used to customize
and improve your visits. Registered members enter basic information
about
themselves to gain the ability to create member profiles,
private and is never shared.
Use of cookies:
AncientFaces uses cookies for registered member sessions. The
information is erased once you leave the site.
When you sign
in to your profile as a registered member, a cookie is
activated to let our web site know that you are logged in.
This enables your membership functions. Without cookies, we
wouldn't be able to tell if you were signed in or not.
Does AncientFaces Share the Information it receives?
AncientFaces never shares any of our visitors'
personal information.
However, please be aware that
when you post information to AncientFaces certain
information is made available online so that visitors
who are interested in your material can contact you to
discuss your submission.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
AncientFaces is dedicated to protecting your personal
information.
AncientFaces uses Secure-Socket Layer (SSL)
encryption to keep your personal information safe. SSL is an
security.
What Information Can I Access?
AncientFaces gives you access to certain information about you
for
the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases,
updating that
information. You can find this information in
'Your Profile' if you are a member.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions.
If
you choose to visit AncientFaces, your visit and any
disputes over
privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and
our Terms and Conditions of use,
including limitations on
damages, arbitration of disputes, and
application of the law
of the state of California. If you have any concern about
privacy at AncientFaces, please submit a request at our Contact Us page. Our
business changes constantly and this policy along with the
Terms and Conditions of use will also change.
SITE POLICIES, MODIFICATION, AND SEVERABILITY
Please review our other policies, such as our Privacy Policy,
posted on this site. These policies also govern your visit to AncientFaces. We reserve the right to make
changes to our site, policies, and these Conditions of Use at any time. If any of these conditions
shall be deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that condition shall be
deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining
condition.
Login »
Sign-up »
Help »
About AncientFaces »
Success Stories »
Contact Us »
Genealogy Directory »
Family Photos »
Surname Records »
Copyright © 1999-2020 AncientFaces, LLC. All Rights Reserved
Privacy Statement
Terms of Service
